SAFETY WASHING BECAUSE THE TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION
SAFETY WASHING BECAUSE THE TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT
SAFETY WASHING BECAUSE THE TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC
TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC
TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND
TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI
TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI WILL
TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI WILL BEND
TRENDLINES OF PROGRESS TOWARD AI RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS.
RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS.
RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK
RESEARCH AUTOMATION AT ANTHROPIC AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU.
AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU.
AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU. CHAIR
AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY:
AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK
AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU
AND OPENAI WILL BEND DOWNWARDS. THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY
THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY
THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH
THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO
THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL
THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE
THANK YOU. CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES.
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES.
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE
CHAIR HAWLEY: THANK YOU VERY MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD,
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD,
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM
MUCH TO ALL THE WITNESSES. I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT
I JUST NOTE FOR THE RECORD, THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY,
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT
THERE IS ONE WITNESS WHOM WE INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS
INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS
INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM
INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN
INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF
INVITED THAT YOU WILL NOT BE HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI.
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI.
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR
HEARING FROM TODAY, AND THAT IS SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE,
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL
SAM ALTMAN OF OPENAI. WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF
WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF
WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU
WE EXTEND AN INVITATION FOR HIM TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU WANTED.
TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU WANTED.
TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU WANTED. HE
TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU WANTED. HE TURNED
TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US
TO BE HERE, DO HIS OWN PANEL IF YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US DOWN.
YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US DOWN.
YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US DOWN. I
YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK
YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S
YOU WANTED. HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE
HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE
HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE
HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE
HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN
HE TURNED US DOWN. I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE
I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO
I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW
I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY
I THINK THAT'S UNFORTUNATE BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF
BECAUSE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES,
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US
DESERVE TO KNOW EXACTLY WHAT'S GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE
GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE
GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT
GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF
GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY
GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT
GOING ON AT ALL OF THESE COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT
COMPANIES, AND TO GIVE US THE SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST
SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST
SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT,
SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT
SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO
SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE
SORT OF TRANSPARENCY THAT I THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN
THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN
THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING
THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF
THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT
THINK IS NEEDED FOR NOT JUST COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE
COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE
COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES
COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT
COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE
COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE
COMFORT, BUT TO HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE
UNDERSTANDING OF WHAT THESE COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD,
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD,
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH
COMPANIES THAT ARE THE MOST POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE
POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE
POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST
POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL
POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY
POWERFUL COMPANIES IN THE WORLD, ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER
ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER
ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN
ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO
ARE DOING RIGHT NOW WITH THE MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN.
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN.
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING
MOST POWERFUL TECHNOLOGY EVER KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND
KNOWN TO MAN. I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I
I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I
I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE
I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT
I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S
I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING
I HOPE THAT HE'LL BE WILLING TO TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE
TALK WITH US IN THE FUTURE AND I HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE
HOPE THAT TODAY'S HEARING WILL HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND
HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND
HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE
HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE OTHER
HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE OTHER EXECUTIVES
HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED
HELP SET THE TABLE FOR THE KINDS OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO
OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO
OF QUESTIONS THAT I THINK HE AND THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER.
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER.
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER. WITH
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER. WITH THAT,
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL START
THE OTHER EXECUTIVES NEED TO ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH
ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH
ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS
ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS OF
ANSWER. WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS OF QUESTIONS.
WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS OF QUESTIONS.
WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS OF QUESTIONS. WE
WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS OF QUESTIONS. WE WILL
WITH THAT, WE WILL START WITH ROUNDS OF QUESTIONS. WE WILL DO